classicheartland.com 2017-05-21

# ClassicHeartland.com Privacy Policy

**The ClassicHeartland.com Privacy Policy**

•ClassicHeartland.com will never share, sell, rent or in any other way distribute any personal information entered by our users into our servers for any reason whatsoever. Collected information is for the sole purpose of awarding prizes.

•ClassicHeartland.com will only contact you regarding shipment of prizes. By submitting your personal information on ClassicHeartland.com, you will not be automatically subscribed to any emailings, postal mailings, etc.

•After the awarding of prizes, all personal information collected from entrants of a particular contest by the ClassicHeartland.com servers is deleted.

•This Website may use ‘cookies’ to collect visitor information. A cookie is a list of characters that can be written to a single file on the end–user’s computer hard drive when the user visits a Web site. Only the Web site that sets the cookie can read it, and it can only be used as a record keeping device to store information that the site already contains. It is unable to read other information from the user’s hard drive.

•Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.

•Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to this Website's users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

•Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

•This privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice.
